<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Projects on Mason Zhang</title>
    <link>https://zhangmason.github.io/projects/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Projects on Mason Zhang</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <copyright>&lt;a href=&#34;https://creativecommons.org/licenses/by-nc/4.0/&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener&#34;&gt;CC BY-NC 4.0&lt;/a&gt;</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 28 Mar 2022 00:00:00 -0500</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://zhangmason.github.io/projects/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Keyboards</title>
      <link>https://zhangmason.github.io/projects/keyboards-2022/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 28 Mar 2022 00:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://zhangmason.github.io/projects/keyboards-2022/</guid>
      <description>Intro During the summer of 2020, I stumbled upon the mechanical keyboard hobby. I had heard about it before, but wrote it off as a waste of money. Who&amp;rsquo;d spend 150 bucks on some plastic keycaps?
I guess having an engineering income changes you - I&amp;rsquo;d end up spending a few thousand in total on all my keyboard purchases.
From the very beginning, the keyboard I had my eyes on was the Satisfaction75.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Art 2022</title>
      <link>https://zhangmason.github.io/projects/2022-art-journey/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 01 Jan 2022 00:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://zhangmason.github.io/projects/2022-art-journey/</guid>
      <description>Intro For the longest time, I&amp;rsquo;ve wanted to get into art. Every once in a while, I&amp;rsquo;d see amazing concept art online and get a brief burst of inspiration. I&amp;rsquo;d think to myself, &amp;ldquo;Damn, I wanna make something like that. But then I&amp;rsquo;d think about all the time and effort necessary to get to a professional level, and I&amp;rsquo;d give up before starting.
I don&amp;rsquo;t know what changed, but at the end of last year (late December 2021), I finally found the motivation to get started.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Website</title>
      <link>https://zhangmason.github.io/projects/website/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 25 Jun 2018 00:10:00 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://zhangmason.github.io/projects/website/</guid>
      <description>Inspiration I&amp;rsquo;ve been meaning to make a website for a while. In college, the thought process was to create a digital portfolio to showcase my worth. Now that I&amp;rsquo;ve graduated and have some time to kill before starting work, it&amp;rsquo;s mostly just a fun project for self-improvement purposes and to practice writing. I figured I could document all of my hobby projects and share some of my thoughts online rather than letting everything sit on a hard drive, for my eyes only.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>