<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Mason Zhang</title>
    <link>https://zhangmason.github.io/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Mason Zhang</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <copyright>&lt;a href=&#34;https://creativecommons.org/licenses/by-nc/4.0/&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener&#34;&gt;CC BY-NC 4.0&lt;/a&gt;</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 06 Jul 2019 10:00:00 -0700</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://zhangmason.github.io/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>College</title>
      <link>https://zhangmason.github.io/thoughts/college/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 06 Jul 2019 10:00:00 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://zhangmason.github.io/thoughts/college/</guid>
      <description>This morning, I woke up at 4:30 to drop my family off at the airport. I didn&amp;rsquo;t get much sleep last night - I wasn&amp;rsquo;t really tired until 11, and then I stayed up for another hour when the Kawhi/PG news broke. It was a 45 minute drive to the airport and too early for anyone to feel like talking much. Spent some time hugging everyone and saying goodbye, and that was it.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>About</title>
      <link>https://zhangmason.github.io/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 25 Jun 2019 20:19:21 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://zhangmason.github.io/about/</guid>
      <description>Hi, I&amp;rsquo;m Mason, a recent Duke graduate and currently an embedded systems engineer at Ayar Labs. Accomplishments include building a chess-playing robot, surviving six weeks in K-ville, and making top 10 on the Pokemon Showdown doubles ladder.
I made this website to write about personal projects and thoughts, so for anything career-related, visit my LinkedIn. If you want to provide feedback, recommend movies, or discuss why the Timberwolves are bad, feel free to contact me on social media or by email.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Ratings 2019</title>
      <link>https://zhangmason.github.io/thoughts/ratings-2019/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Jan 2019 10:00:21 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://zhangmason.github.io/thoughts/ratings-2019/</guid>
      <description>Intro Towards the end of 2018, I took a larger interest in films, largely thanks to a few friends who showed me the amount of thought, planning, and technology that goes into crafting a good movie. I figured I might as well document what I&amp;rsquo;ve seen. My average rating as of June is 7.13. I think that&amp;rsquo;s reasonable, since I generally choose to watch good movies.
Ratings are accompanied by a few paragraphs of my thoughts and are spoiler free, except for drop-down sections labelled as such.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Portal Mirrors</title>
      <link>https://zhangmason.github.io/projects/portal-mirrors/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 26 Jun 2018 00:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://zhangmason.github.io/projects/portal-mirrors/</guid>
      <description>Inspiration Placeholder. Planning to make some Portal mirrors to decorate my room once I settle down in California. Inspired by this video.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Website</title>
      <link>https://zhangmason.github.io/projects/website/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 25 Jun 2018 00:10:00 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://zhangmason.github.io/projects/website/</guid>
      <description>Inspiration I&amp;rsquo;ve been meaning to make a website for a while. In college, the thought process was to create a digital portfolio to showcase my worth. Now that I&amp;rsquo;ve graduated and have some time to kill before starting work, it&amp;rsquo;s mostly just a fun project for self-improvement purposes and to practice writing. I figured I could document all of my hobby projects and share some of my thoughts online rather than letting everything sit on a hard drive, for my eyes only.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>