<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>ratings on Mason Zhang</title>
    <link>https://zhangmason.github.io/tags/ratings/</link>
    <description>Recent content in ratings on Mason Zhang</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <copyright>&lt;a href=&#34;https://creativecommons.org/licenses/by-nc/4.0/&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener&#34;&gt;CC BY-NC 4.0&lt;/a&gt;</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 01 Jan 2022 10:00:21 -0500</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://zhangmason.github.io/tags/ratings/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Ratings 2022</title>
      <link>https://zhangmason.github.io/thoughts/ratings-2022/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 01 Jan 2022 10:00:21 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://zhangmason.github.io/thoughts/ratings-2022/</guid>
      <description>Intro Nothing new to say once again, just more content that I&amp;rsquo;ve consumed. REVIEWS CONTAIN SPOILERS.
Ratings Matrix 2: 7 / 10 I liked Matrix 2 even more than the first Matrix. With the scene already set, we get to dive even deeper into the Matrix, following fully unleased Neo and Agent Smith, among other charismatic characters (I love the Keymaker). Matrix 2 features even better production quality, hype extended fights, and a layered story with a lot of moving parts.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Ratings 2021</title>
      <link>https://zhangmason.github.io/thoughts/ratings-2021/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 01 Jan 2021 10:00:21 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://zhangmason.github.io/thoughts/ratings-2021/</guid>
      <description>Intro Nothing new to say, just more content that I&amp;rsquo;ve consumed. REVIEWS CONTAIN SPOILERS.
Ratings Avatar: The Last Airbender: 8 / 10 Book 1: 6 / 10 I was bored, browsed Netflix, saw this, figured I&amp;rsquo;d see what all the hype was about. I&amp;rsquo;d say this first arc was mostly just setup. Don&amp;rsquo;t get me wrong, the characters, world-building, and general atmosphere are great. But nothing much of substance happens barring the first few and last few episodes.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Ratings 2020</title>
      <link>https://zhangmason.github.io/thoughts/ratings-2020/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 01 Jan 2020 10:00:21 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://zhangmason.github.io/thoughts/ratings-2020/</guid>
      <description>Intro I&amp;rsquo;m mixing things up this year. Instead of purely spoiler-free movie ratings, this year we&amp;rsquo;re rating everything entertainment. Movies, TV shows, books, anime, and video games. Write-ups will be much more free-form and likely full of spoilers. In the end, this list is moreso for me than anyone else, so read at your own risk I guess. REVIEWS CONTAIN SPOILERS.
Ratings The Tatami Galaxy: 6 / 10 Oh boy, first review of the year.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Ratings 2019</title>
      <link>https://zhangmason.github.io/thoughts/ratings-2019/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Jan 2019 10:00:21 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://zhangmason.github.io/thoughts/ratings-2019/</guid>
      <description>Intro Towards the end of 2018, I took a larger interest in films, largely thanks to a few friends who showed me the amount of thought and creativity that goes into a good movie. I figured I might as well document what I&amp;rsquo;ve seen. Average movie rating for 2019 came out to 6.85. Makes sense. Watched a lot great stuff this year.
Ratings are accompanied by a few paragraphs of my thoughts and are spoiler free, except for drop-down sections labelled as such.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>